So far in our hotel dialogue we've been able to confirm the dates.
到目前为止，在我们的酒店对话中，我们已经能够确认日期。
We've also been able to confirm the number of guests and we've talked about the different room types
我们还能够确认客人的数量，并讨论了不同的房间类型
and the prices.
和价格。
So now it's time to decide before we decide where the guest before we decide which room type we might
所以现在是时候在我们决定客人去哪里之前再决定我们可以选择哪种房型了
want to know how much the suite room is probably pretty expensive.
想知道套间大概多少钱，挺贵的。
It's three hundred and twenty dollars per night each night.
每晚每晚三百二十美元。
Three hundred and twenty.
三百二十。
Well that's pretty expensive and maybe that's a bit out of my price range.
嗯，这很贵，也许这有点超出我的价格范围。
It's a bit out of my price range.
这有点超出我的价格范围。
All right.
好的。
Now I've tried to make this as natural as possible.
现在我试图让它尽可能自然。
I've tried to make it as realistic as possible so by adding things like Mm hmm.
我试图通过添加诸如 Mm hmm 之类的东西使其尽可能逼真。
All right.
好的。
It's not really adding a lot of meaning but it is adding what people often say when they're in this
它并没有真正增加很多意义，但它增加了人们在这个过程中经常说的话
kind of conversation is what we use when we think all right is when we've decided something or when
当我们认为一切正常时，当我们决定某事或何时
we've agreed to something.
我们已经同意了一些事情。
All right I guess I guess.
好吧，我猜我猜。
And again this doesn't really add anything either.
同样，这也没有真正添加任何东西。
We often just add I guess to things to soften what we're saying or when we're not really sure we're
我们经常只是在某些事情上加上我猜想来软化我们所说的话，或者当我们不确定我们是
not really confident about what we want to say.
对我们想说的话没有信心。
I guess I'll have.
我想我会的。
Well I guess I'll have a burger.
好吧，我想我会吃一个汉堡。
You're not really sure.
你不太确定。
So I guess we'll go with go with means choose choose.
所以我想我们会用 go with 表示选择选择。
I guess we'll go with the deluxe room as long as it has Wi-Fi.
我想我们会选择豪华房，只要它有 Wi-Fi。
So there is a now condition a condition if it has Wi-Fi I'll stay there if it doesn't I won't.
所以现在有一个条件，如果它有 Wi-Fi，我会呆在那里，如果没有，我不会。
Of course it has Wi-Fi.
当然它有Wi-Fi。
It's the 21st century.
这是21世纪。
It's got to have Wi-Fi.
它必须有Wi-Fi。
Could we get it higher up the Wi-Fi.
我们能不能让它在 Wi-Fi 上更高。
No we're talking about the room.
不，我们在谈论房间。
We could say could we get a room that's higher up.
我们可以说我们能不能得到一个更高的房间。
Could we get a room in an upper floor an upper floor.
我们能不能在楼上的楼上找个房间。
We could say that too but could we get it higher up.
我们也可以这么说，但我们能不能让它更高。
They will know what we mean.
他们会明白我们的意思。
We want a view.
我们想要一个视图。
We want a room with a view if possible.
如果可能的话，我们想要一个有风景的房间。
Now that's just a preference a preference is when maybe we have three choices A B and C but I RIGHT
现在这只是一种偏好，一种偏好是当我们可能有三个选择 A B 和 C 但我对
SEE THERE A B and C and A is the preference but B is OK to maybe C is OK but a is our preference so
看到那里 A B 和 C 和 A 是偏好，但 B 可以，也许 C 可以，但 a 是我们的偏好，所以
if there are two rooms one on the tenth floor and the one on the 30th floor they're both deluxe rooms.
如果有两间房，一间在十楼，一间在三十楼，都是豪华房。
They both have Wi-Fi.
他们都有Wi-Fi。
They're the same price.
它们的价格相同。
Well I'm gonna choose my preference would be to have the one on the higher floor not the one on the
好吧，我会选择我的偏好是在较高楼层而不是在
lower floor.
较低的楼层。
OK.
好的。
It's just a preference.
这只是一种偏好。
I'll take either one if I have to but that one is better because I like the view OK.
如果必须的话，我会选择其中一个，但那个更好，因为我喜欢这里的景色。
So we use if possible when we want to state our preferences.
因此，当我们想要陈述我们的偏好时，我们会尽可能使用。
Sure.
当然。
I can book a deluxe room on the 24th floor if that works and yes it does have Wi-Fi.
如果可行，我可以预订 24 楼的豪华房，而且确实有 Wi-Fi。
It does have Wi-Fi.
它确实有无线网络。
So we're doing all that together.
所以我们一起做这一切。
And I realized I forgot to mark who's saying what I think you can guess here but let's just do that.
我意识到我忘了标记谁在说我认为你可以在这里猜到的内容，但让我们这样做。
How much is the how much is the suite.
套房多少钱。 这是客人说的。
It's three hundred and twenty dollars per night.
每晚三百二十美元。
That is the receptionist.
那是接待员。
All right.
好的。
That's the guest.
那是客人。
And then the receptionist is confirming.
然后接待员正在确认。62
Sure means that's OK I can book the book.
当然意味着没关系，我可以预订这本书。
That means there are probably several rooms on maybe the 24th floor or on higher floors on the 24th
这意味着可能有几个房间可能在 24 楼或 24 楼更高的楼层
floor.
地面。
If that works and yes it does have Wi-Fi.
如果可行，是的，它确实有 Wi-Fi。
Do you have any questions that means about other things.
您对其他事情有任何疑问吗？
For example we've got the room now.
例如，我们现在有了房间。
It's set.
设置好了。
It's all good.
都很好。
I've got your preferences.
我有你的喜好。
I've booked the room that you want.
我已经预订了你想要的房间。
It's on the 24th floor.
它在 24 楼。
That's pretty good.
这很不错。
Sure confirms it.
肯定证实了。
And then if that works is to say if you have any problems with me doing this I'm doing it now.
然后，如果这行得通，就是说如果你对我这样做有任何问题，我现在就这样做。
The receptionist is doing it now.
接待员现在正在做。
If there are any issues with me doing that now say it now.
如果我这样做有任何问题，现在就说出来。
Say wait wait wait.
说等等等等。
No no no.
不不不。
The 20 Twenty fourth floor is not high enough for example but it saves time.
例如20 20 4楼不够高，但它节省了时间。
We can get through the interaction faster if I don't need to say is that OK because you've told me that
如果我不需要说没关系，我们可以更快地完成互动，因为你已经告诉我了
you want a deluxe room on the 24th floor or a higher floor so I can assume that what I'm going to do
你想要一间 24 楼或更高楼层的豪华房，所以我可以假设我要做什么
now is OK.
现在好了。
OK.
好的。
And yes it does have Wi-Fi.
是的，它确实有 Wi-Fi。
Do you have any questions.
你有任何问题吗。
It's a very common question to ask to make sure that all of the needs of the guest are met.
确保满足客人的所有需求是一个非常常见的问题。
If you're not really confident in your English and you're in this situation one good idea might be to
如果你对自己的英语不是很自信，而且你处于这种情况下，一个好主意可能是
write down your questions before you call.
在打电话之前写下您的问题。
That way you can focus on being polite and getting the really important things correct like the type
这样，您就可以专注于保持礼貌并正确处理真正重要的事情，例如类型
of room and the dates.
房间和日期。
And then you don't have to try to remember your questions.
然后你不必试图记住你的问题。
If you if you don't feel very confident to to do the English situation if you need to do this.
如果你对做英语的情况不是很有信心的话，如果你需要这样做的话。
Write your questions down.
写下你的问题。
That's my advice.
这是我的建议。
That's just personal personal advice.
这只是个人的个人建议。